If you stuck a cup deep into the ocean
and brought it back up again, it would
be full of little bits of DNA that we
can use to discover what animals are
down there. But when they really did
this, guess how much of the DNA was
unknown. We don't know what animal it
came from. The answer is 90%.
They call it dark taxa. It might be from
animals that we know about but never
genome. Or it might be from something
entirely new. Researchers are starting
to use machine learning to fill in those
gaps. And the hope is that they can use
this dark taxa to group them with
similar DNA. So you can start to say,
"This looks like squid. Is it new
squid?" So to see what they're actually
finding, subscribe.